<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="title">Beatles Analogy Vol.1</string>

    <string name="text">The Beatles Anthology is the www.grammy.com Grammy Award winning 3 part mini series that tells, in the Beatles own words, the dramatic and astonishing story of the most influential band in rock history.

The Anthology charts the official history of the Beatles from their earliest days in Liverpool up to the break up of the group in 1970. Using a mixture of archive footage, home movies, never before seen concert footage and unheard studio tracks, together with interviews with the Beatles themselves, the Anthology invites you as John Lennon would say into the eye of the hurricane
    Approximately coinciding with the release of the "Free as a Bird" single and Anthology 1 album (the first of three double-CD albums), The Beatles Anthology series of documentaries was broadcast on ITV in the United Kingdom and ABC television in the United States in 1995. The Anthology series takes a form similar to that of the Anthology book, by being a series of first-person accounts by the Beatles themselves, with no external "objective" narration. Footage in the Anthology series features voice-over recordings of all four Beatles to push the narrative of the story, with contributions from their producer, road manager and others. As well as telling their story through archival footage, Paul McCartney, George Harrison and Ringo Starr appear in interview segments recorded exclusively for the series; John Lennon appears only in historic archival footage. The Beatles wives, past and present, do not appear (excluding archival footage such as video from India and the music video for Harrisons song "Something").

The series, which included over five thousand hours of planning and production, is composed of numerous film clips and interviews that present a complete history of the band from the Beatles own personal perspectives. When it aired on ABC, the series comprised six hour-long programs, aired on three nights in November 1995. The series was later released, as eight expanded episodes, on VHS, laserdisc and as a boxed set of five DVDs (4 discs with 2 episodes apiece and a disc of extras).</string>
</resources>